rschooltoday.com 2017-10-15

# Privacy Statement - Privacy Policy - rSchoolToday.com

Privacy Policy - rSchoolToday                      Last modified March 2017

This privacy policy sets forth how “rSchoolToday” uses and protects any information that you give “rSchoolToday” when you use this website or any of our applications.

“rSchoolToday” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website or any of our applications, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

Please note that by accessing this website or any of our applications, you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy.

“rSchoolToday” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Please check this page periodically to ensure that you agree with any updates. 

We may collect information such as: name and job title, contact information including email address, demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests and other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

We collect this information, “Personal Information” from now on, to understand your needs and we may use the Personal Information to improve our products and services, and in particular for the following reasons: internal record keeping, we may periodically send emails about new products or features, special offers or other using the Personal Information you have provided.   
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or phone.

We will never sell your information.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure.

Security  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we have no control over any other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by emailing us at [info@rschooltoday.com](mailto:info@rschooltoday.com)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.
